LUCAS PADILHA

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



PERSONAL INFORMATIONS

- Praceta Verderena 9, Barreiro
- +351 912 015 235
- lucas padilha@icloud.com

ABOUT (PROFESSIONAL) ME

I am a guy passionate by numbers, logical thinking and hard issues to fix. All of my professional experience (in a lot of different areas) was made with this mindset and now I am pretty sure that kind of thinking can change wherever environment that you are.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Le Wagon - Lisbon (Portugal)

Full-stack web development | 2019

- RoR
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- SQL,
- Git, GitHub
- Heroku

FMU FISP - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

Civil Engineering Degree | Feb 2012 - Jan 2015

- Numerical Calculation
- Structural Calculation
- Physics
- Mathematics

CNA - São Paulo - SP (Brazil)

English Course | Jan 2009 - Dec 2011

LANGUAGES

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Logistics and Warehouse Manager

Brodheim Group | Jul 2017 - Oct 2019 (Portugal)

- Commodity Management
- Partial and general inventories
- Logistic control between chain stores
- Contacts with suppliers

Math and Physics teacher

Centro de explicações Primavera | Jan 2017 - Jul 2017

- Tutoring and classes, in math and physics, for students from 1st to 12th grade.

Team Coordinator

Thousand Solutions | Mar 2016 - Jan 2017 (Portugal)

- Direct customer acquisition for energy business contracts
- Manage team for this same function
- Lead daily morning meetings

Salesperson and Submanager

Levi Strauss & CO | Jan 2014 - Dec 2015 (Brazil)

- People management
- Sell products to the public

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Co-founder of WALD project, a computer programming that creates a Rails WebApp with just the visual schema. Check us on:

□ waldproject.com